This Raili Minister Azan Netanya is dead and has been connected
Is this news hot on the social media of the world at this time?
And some people say that he is dead and his AI best Fake Deep Fecorios is also brought to the world.
And some people say that he is Marani
But he is in a coma and regarding this, he is showing the security questions of the hospital in front of the world
Well, it was said that to understand this, the former understand that the past is present in its own place
And that's because Netanya was supposed to have a meeting this week
With one of Eves' orders that the battle be discussed, some fees would be negated
But that meeting was canceled by this royal
The thing to understand now is that there are encounters in war
There is also cancellation and cancellation
So this is not a proof
But let's see from one day that Netanya has done it in the last week
No public explanation has been given
And Iran was making noise at that time and saying Iran
That Netanya Hoon's faith is unklee
Or it should be understood that
U.S. Secretary of State Ayuf Vat Peet Haksat recently said that Iran's leadership had ended.
So what did Dini Ran's leadership do next?
Spring in the rain with people and make videos with people
He gave his proof
But Netanya Hoon's proof did not come
And Israel's media as proof
Netanya Hoon Ke Aath video has been released
He was answering the questions of the wallet
That is, there is still no public perception
And the video that belongs to Sher
Answers take this video to forensics
So you see she looks like a twenty-something giant
What is Netanya Haun, instead of five, six is ​​used
And we see you in Dev on the jogos
Apart from Ki Che Aglaya, following Netanya Hoon
Some things disappear and some things appear
That is, if it is also an Eai Bes Dev
So it is questionable that Natanya has said
There are two directions
As proof of the people talking
Vekhe that Eves Secretary Besand
There is one Antanya and I am this Antanya
Am I cute?
Antonia Hoon's Eaves Prasdin Durantrup will call you in the consultation room
A Besand said that I am Antonia
And will walk away
But when Eves Secretary Besand
Came back after a few hours to Antanya Hoon
So their number was spoken
Phrases have been in the mill for a long time
Such mustard
But the President is in great spirits
The Iranian Mission is proceeding well ahead of schedule
and I have to tell you well that I have a teenager
who is considering
This opinion government tweeted about Netanya Haun
And he wrote this
There is a lot going on about Netanya's fate
To confirm and communicate
Choice of effort
And then Chinhi was made Dalit
With this reason, people doubt and read
That I am Akhin Netanya
Where is what?
Come on, think about it
This story has begun
Many days ago today
When this Royal decided that we would run one of our Pentagons
But they will not make the same mistake that America did
We do not have our Pentagon above ground
We will drive our Pentagon underground
There is a street inside Central Talavif
whose name is
Lanado Devenshee Street
If this street you will try to read google father
So you won't see anything
Take that street
If something like this is happening on this street
Which is much higher than yours and mine total
Inside S Street
When the first chalk arrives inside Lanado-Devenshi Street
Phapar is an emirate
And this building is named
The Devonshi Complex
This is the decision of six thousand square meters
Site it within this royale
called wool
This is called an electromagnet shell
Underbrun is intelligence saturated
And this is what you need to know about it
That the case put money on him
Thoughts Eves a steaks Monday
And this to you from Eves' hidden file
It would also be clear from the constitution document
It is questionable why this Royal made this decision
That if everything in the world ends
May you be blessed with the city above
So this pit which is pitted in this royal
Even then this pit exists
And from here, it is a war
Neovivoctims were given a controlled single session
This decision is also written by Navioctimus
That it decides in such a way that it is full of knowledge
And here seventy people sit at the same time
In front of big screens
And take decisions about war
And it works in shifts
And that's where the decisions of this Royal Screaming Position are sewn
Now comes a contrasting point
In June two thousand fifty five
This was a war between the United States and Iran
So Iran fired some missiles
And that's what the puttler decides
It is six thousand square meters
Exactly equal to it
It is known that the council will give the bill
This is the menstruf defense of this royale
Which is also called Kariya in this Royal
And within this ryal is also called the fortres fizeyn
This Royal did this yesterday in June two thousand fifty five
That we have attacked Kariya
silence
There was complete silence from this Royal
And then after five days the Jerusalem posse rebooted
Yes, there has been an attack on Kariya
And since then this Raila
All images of this Raila Strayed
Google refused to bring it up
Shut down the cameras
The state was cordoned off
And did the same
That the Principal House needs renovation
We are currently doing renovation work
You were doing renovation work
Or you do your own thing
And were repairing this site ativan
Now the thing to understand here is Patakya
It is understandable that since this year
Kills by going kilometers away
That action is gone
That is, on the same site, the site is run on Ativan
So passion is created
That Ben Gower who
I am Benjamin Nathan
Which is Chris in the decision
They were in this site ativan
And Shire they are no more
Now here is a question
Is Nitin or Hoon time M dead or not?
So also Ans Badiou
I don't know
This also happens
That it be an out and of this Royal
Be a secret
But now the heart is right
Or it is questionable to me at this point
That if it is natan or hoon marge is
or if missing
is in a coma
Not dead
At this time, the United States
What options does Dantalram have?
At that time to Danaltrum
Only two eggs are laid
The first option is this
That he should do the trick and say that
We have lost this battle
And we don't want to fight anymore
And the second option is this
That he would be ready to fight more
First let's look at the first option
If danaltram
By coming to this session
They decide
That there is no more war
We have lost
So what will be the result?
The pattern
Iran will ask you for compensation
Will ask for reparations
It will cease to exist
That will be Pisayagi Aran Shift
So within the next five to ten years
Iran will be pregnant
Iran will start to make the road
And Allardy
Erdji will chase the corridor
Erdji would have been drinking
And this talk is going to be digested by America
Nice Royal is about to be digested
And when that happens
So America's economy will begin to collapse
and by τ Trump or M. Pachilt
or by mither vellection
Moe will have to eat
Now what is the second option?
The second option is that your presidency
And to save your life
To save this presidency
In which Aoldi his twenty-second presidency
Jedi Evans began to speak
That I celebrated
I didn't say that
My paths are straight
A messy conversation has begun
To save this life
Eve to save the Presidency
Give the crown of bodhisattvas
To save your life and your economy
will use
So here it is important to go
Maybe they like it
Zada will be first
What do you say?
Raise the revolution
This verse
Day Abroad
So maybe America is abroad
Will do
But if America
The crown of the Bodhisattvas descends
So E-Ran has only one answer to this
Which is the foreign assistant of E-Ran
Now ha sir has done a chi oldi
Baby or no baby?
Darryl Ron Bodson's Grand Attar
Or don't get off
But one thing
They stayed awake that night
And that this war is now
You don't have Wally
Against xinizin
This war of Islam
Just got old